我想区分称为图像处理的技术，和
I’d like to make a distinction between the techniques known as image processing, and
被称为计算机视觉的技术。图像处理是一种需要的技术
the techniques known as computer vision. Image processing is a technique that takes
一个图像，并产生另一个图像。它通常用于图像增强。在这
an image and produces another image. It’s often used for image enhancement. In this
例如，我们看到一个医学图像，其中身体内的特征相当模糊，并且
example we see a medical image where features within the body are rather indistinct, and
通过对其应用图像处理技术，它们得到了增强。他们有
by applying an image processing technique to it, they have been enhanced. They have
更高的对比度，更容易看到身体内的电线和其他结构。
higher contrast and it is easier to see the wires and other structures inside the body.
另一方面，计算机视觉，或者有时被称为机器视觉，需要一个
Computer vision, on the other hand, or machine vision as it’s sometimes called, takes an
图像和生成功能。我们在这里看到的是具有大量彩色的输入图像
image and produces features. What we see here is an input image with a large number of coloured
像素。有些是黄色的，有些是灰色的，有些是蓝色的。它正在生产什么
pixels. Some are yellow, some are grey, some are blue. And what it’s producing on the
右侧是仅描述黄色物体的特征。我们可以在这里看到
right-hand side are features which describe just the yellow objects. And we can see here
我们已经突出了这些物体的中心，我们也放了红框
that we’ve highlighted the centres of those objects, and we’ve also put red boxes around
它们显示了它们的空间范围。所以我们减少了整体信息量
them that show their spatial extent. So we’ve reduced the amount of information from a whole
很多颜色像素到一堆非常简洁的中心和坐标坐标信息
lot of colour pixels to a bunch of quite succinct information for coordinates of centres and
四个边界框角落的坐标。
the coordinates of the corners of four bounding boxes.
我们称之为图像特征的相关信息实际上有三个
That pertinent information we refer to as image features and there are really three
常用的不同类型的图像功能。第一个是地区;该
different kinds of image features that are in common use. The first one is regions; the
我刚刚给出的例子。对于这些黄色物体中的每一个，我可能都有兴趣知道
example that I just gave. For each of these yellow objects, I might be interested in knowing
他们的中心在哪里，他们有多大，他们的形状是什么，方向是什么。
where’s their centre, how big are they, what shape are they, what’s the orientation.
它们是否指向侧面，是否垂直指向。还有其他功能
Are they pointing sideways, are they pointing vertically. And there are other features that
我们可以用它来描述这些黄色物体的形状。
we could use to describe the shape of these yellow objects.
另一种非常常见的特征是线条。线条无处不在。肯定在
Another kind of very common feature are lines. And lines are everywhere. certainly in the
建设环境。所以我们可能会对这些主导的方程式感兴趣
built environment. So we might be interested in what are the equations of these dominant
图像中的线条。我们可能对这些线的起点和终点感兴趣，
lines in the image. We might be interested in the start and end points of these lines,
可能划定屋顶区域或建筑物边缘的线段。
the line segments that perhaps might delineate an area of a roof or the edge of a building.
我们在计算机视觉中使用的最后一种功能是点。我在这里做的是
The last kind of feature that we use in computer vision are points. Here what I’ve done is
覆盖在建筑物的图片上，称为兴趣点。这些是要点
overlaid onto a picture of a building what are called interest points. These are points
它包含大量信息，并且很容易在另一个视图中找到
that contain a lot of information and would be easy to find in another view of that same
建造。所以圆圈表示这些兴趣点的中心和大小
building. So the circles indicate the centre of these interest points and the size of the
圈子说明了这些兴趣点的规模。现在，兴趣点和
circle says something about the scale of those interest points. Now, interest points and
我们将在本系列讲座中介绍积分的规模，但是
the scale of points is not something we’re going to cover in this lecture series, but
当然这是一个关于哪些文献很多的话题，而且它们是非常的
certainly it’s a topic about which there is a lot of literature, and they are a very
现代计算机视觉中的重要概念。让我们再回过头来考虑一下地区
important concept in modern computer vision. Let’s go back again and consider region
功能，这是我们将在本讲座中讨论的内容。你可能会有一个问题
features, which is what we are going to talk about in this lecture. A question you might
想问一下这个标志上的符号在哪里;字母和其他字母在哪里
like to ask is where are the symbols on this sign; where are the letters and the other
图形元素。好吧，如果我们找到区域功能，我们就能解决这个问题。
graphical elements. Well if we find region features we are able to solve this problem.
而我在这里用一些非常简单的代码完成的工作就是放置一个边界框
And what I’ve done here with a bit of quite simple code, is to put a bounding box around
这个黑色标志上的每个不同的白色符号。
each of the distinct white symbols on this otherwise black sign.